<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>	<title>Zoner</title>
	<description>This is where I write about blogging with Zoner!</description>
	<link>https://zone-builder.neocities.org/</link>
	<atom:link href="https://zone-builder.neocities.org/" rel="self"></atom:link>
	<language>en</language>
	<lastBuildDate>
Wed, 10 Dec 2025 05:16:53 +0000
</lastBuildDate>
	<ttl>1440</ttl>

	<item>
		<title>Toonami Rewind Whats Old Is New Again</title>
		<description>Originally written on May 31, 2024.</description>
		<link>https://zone-builder.neocities.org/posts/2024-05-31-toonami-rewind-whats-old-is-new-again.html</link>
		<pubDate>
			Fri, 31 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000
		</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Toonami Rewind A Failed Experiment</title>
		<description>I’ve been watching Toonami since I was a child, and in some form or another I’ve watched Toonami’s current [as] incarnation since I was in 8th grade. To say that I’m surprised about the current state regarding Toonami Rewind would honestly be a lie, and I’m not even talking about current affairs.</description>
		<link>https://zone-builder.neocities.org/posts/2024-12-21-toonami-rewind-a-failed-experiment.html</link>
		<pubDate>
			Sat, 21 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000
		</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Virtua Insanity</title>
		<description>Virtua Fighter's issue is that in the mainstream, it doesn't get nearly as much respect that I think it deserves.</description>
		<link>https://zone-builder.neocities.org/posts/2025-09-23-virtua-insanity.html</link>
		<pubDate>
			Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000
		</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>2026 Updates</title>
		<description>Hey there, I’m currently writing this as I juggle… a lot. I honestly apologize for the lack of consistent updates. Life has been pretty hectic. I do hope however, that everyone has been okay during this holiday season.</description>
		<link>https://zone-builder.neocities.org/posts/2025-12-04-2026-updates.html</link>
		<pubDate>
			Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000
		</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Tricking Out Anime An Interview With Stu Levy Of Tokyopop</title>
		<description>This was originally made for a video project that I had conceptualized years ago that still remains unpublished. However, I wanted to make sure that the questions I asked were still publicly available since there's information that previously hasn't been discussed.  I still have the original questions with Stu's answers, so remaking this article is thankfully easy.</description>
		<link>https://zone-builder.neocities.org/posts/2025-12-10-tricking-out-anime-an-interview-with-stu-levy-of-tokyopop.html</link>
		<pubDate>
			Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000
		</pubDate>
	</item>

</channel>
</rss>